I never
believed in happy endings.
They were part
of someone else's story.
As if my life
could ever be that simple.
Everyone kept telling me that
London would be a fresh start.
That I needed one.
Especially after everything
that happened.
Twenty years ago, my mom
left England for a man.
Now she was dragging us back
for a different one.
A Prince Charming
in a castle for her,
and a wicked stepbrother for me.
I thought I had it
all figured out,
but I had no idea.
OK, donate or keep?
Er, donate, I guess.
What?!
No, Mr Snuggles, you can't.
Come on, Haley, be ruthless.
All right, fine,
I'm gonna keep him.
He's gonna be the perfect
centrepiece for my Noah shrine.
Speaking of...
Oh, my God.
Here. She is tuned up
and ready for you to...
Burn out?
"Look after"
is what I was going for. OK?
OK. I'll think of you
every time I speed.
OK, nearly done.
Noah's Ark is almost empty.
I just wish I could
take you both with me.
You're lucky Ella
is taking you with her.
There is a purge going on
out front.
Well, Daddy Warbucks
says we'll want for nothing.
That's like an outdated
anti feminist fairy tale.
Yeah, some kind of fairy tale
where the princess
has to leave her frog. Me.
Cute. All right,
I'm gonna go hang
with the vultures in the yard.
Pick at the carcass.
What am I gonna do? I can't
believe you're actually leaving.
I know.
Wait, have you got something
in your eye?
- Shut up.
- Oh, shit!
- It's both eyes.
- Shut up!
You should get that checked out.
Stop. I'm gonna miss you.
Yeah, me, too.
But, listen.
I've heard that long-distance
relationships can be...
- The best.
- hard. Hard.
But, you know, that's
what we're signing up for,
- and it's gonna suck.
- Noah, Noah, I'm in, OK?
Thank God.
OK! OK.
Why do you have to go?
What's in London?
♪ Riding through the city
on my bike all day ♪
♪ Cos the filth
took away my licence ♪
♪ It doesn't get me down
and I feel OK ♪
♪ Cos the sights
that I'm seeing are priceless ♪
♪ Sun is in the sky,
oh why, oh why ♪
♪ Would I wanna be
anywhere else? ♪
♪ Sun is in the sky,
oh why, oh why ♪
♪ Would I wanna be
anywhere else? ♪
♪ When you look with your eyes,
everything seems nice ♪
♪ But if you look twice,
you can see it's all lies ♪
♪ There was a little old lady
who was walking down the road ♪
♪ She was struggling
with bags from Tesco ♪
♪ There were people from the
City having lunch in the park ♪
♪ I believe
that is called al fresco ♪
♪ The sun is in the sky,
oh why, oh why... ♪
I hope you get to meet Nick
this morning.
Or maybe tonight at the gala.
The golden boy?
Well, if you and William
hadn't eloped,
- then we would have met already.
- Noah.
Neither of you
wanted to be there.
He loves his cars, you know.
I think you're gonna like him.
If I don't,
well, I guess it's too bad,
because we'll already
be living together.
Complete strangers
living together.
Could be fun.
Home, sweet home.
Subtle.
Good thing
I practised my curtsey.
- Hello, my darling.
- Welcome home.
How are you?
Just been checking
my speech for tonight.
I take it you want to see me.
I've missed you.
Welcome, Noah.
Did you have a good flight?
We should get you something
to eat. A PB and J?
- Hamburger?
- No, thanks.
OK. We just want you
to feel at home.
Come on.
Noah got to see the sights?
She certainly did.
We got to see everything.
- Come.
- What do you think?
Can't wait to take a twirl
in the ballroom.
Sadly, no ballroom.
But I am confident
that the venue tonight
will impress
even the most discerning critic.
Yes, that would be you.
Martin will show you
to your room.
Follow me.
I'll give you the tour.
♪ The TV's on,
the woman's blonde ♪
♪ She talks and talks
of how the rich are wrong ♪
♪ They cheat on wives,
never pay the price ♪
♪ I'm a low-class guy,
that sounds pretty nice ♪
♪ I want to be with
the bourgeoisieses ♪
♪ I want to be see how
♪ Party all night ♪
♪ I want to be with
the bourgeoisieses ♪
♪ I want to be see how
♪ La-di-dee-die ♪
♪ I want to be with
the bourgeoisieses... ♪
I don't understand
why they're coming.
We don't need them.
Aren't you curious
what she looks like?
No!
♪ I want... ♪
- Nice view, huh?
- What? No. No.
Oh, Noah. Just... enjoy it.
It's pretty special.
And it's nice to see you happy.
This is a new start for us.
Did you see the security system?
This place is a fortress.
He can't get you here.
You're safer here
than you've ever been.
Try and get some rest
before the gala tonight.
Yeah.
Maybe have a bite to eat first?
They've made meatloaf.
Why?
I have no idea.
Shit!
Is that how you greet people
in Florida?
Because here,
we just shake hands.
So you're the infamous
Nicholas Leister.
Yeah. And you're the younger
of the new unwanted guests.
Well, don't flatter yourself.
If I had a choice,
I'd be anywhere but here.
That is not what it looked like
when you gave yourself the tour.
What is taking so long?
I'm parched.
A spoiled daddy's boy
and a stalker. Hmm!
Ouch. Play nice, kids.
How the lowly have risen.
Oh. British charm.
Spare me.
Neither of us want this.
Sorry, Giles, I was just saying
hello to my new stepsister.
- What's your name?
- Noah.
Hmm! Right.
Well, I knew
it was something regrettable.
Well, enjoy your meatloaf, Noah.
Dick.
I think it's probably best we
stay out of each other's way,
- don't you think?
- Works for me.
Hey! Damn.
Hey. Er, just waiting for you
to wake up.
Not that I'm missing you.
I also just met Nick.
He's even worse than we thought.
And Mom's laid out all
of these gowns for this gala
like it's my society debut.
Anyway, er...
Yeah. Love you. Speak soon.
Noah! Let's hustle.
- Got her ready?
- She is, yeah.
Where are they?
What do you think I should say?
Should I sing?
Hey.
You know it's just us,
so the big entrance
wasn't necessary.
You know what else
isn't necessary?
- You being so rude.
- My apologies.
Come on.
Oops.
I'm not gonna rise to it
and give you the satisfaction
you're craving.
That's not a problem.
Your inappropriate attire
is satisfaction enough.
- Ready.
- Ready?
You realise it's black tie,
right?
Thank you.
- I'll meet you guys there, yeah?
- Sure.
How about this for
a first night in London, Noah?
Lovely dress, darling.
Who are you wearing?
Ladies and gentlemen,
climate change is
the defining issue of our time.
Now why are we all gathered here
this evening?
We've heard it before,
but we haven't heard it enough.
Now is the time for action.
Thank you.
You looked like you needed this.
These men and women
have demonstrated...
I'm Giles, by the way.
How are you getting on
with your brother?
Stepbrother.
And as of now, I'd say it's
a feeling of mutual loathing.
Well, you called him
a spoiled little daddy's boy.
I think it rather ruffled
his duck down.
I call it as I see it.
Hmm.
No, Nick is a lot of things,
but he's not spoiled.
He makes his own moolah.
You've heard of Connect.
The ride-sharing app?
Two people going
in the same direction,
one hitches a ride
with the other?
Over one million users.
He sold the business
when he was 17
and made lots and lots
of bloody money.
Thanks.
He's no nepo freeloader
like the rest of us.
So what does he do now?
Let's just say, he's on
a voyage of self-discovery.
Ciao.
Oh, my God,
did you hear about Annabel?
- No.
- She didn't get into Oxford.
- It's so embarrassing.
- That's awful.
The only sure way
to get into a good uni
is to go to a private school.
I mean, Noah, where do you
stand on selective education?
Noah's taking a year out,
and then she's applying to UCL.
That's where I go!
You'll love it. I'll give you
all the insider goss.
Where to drink, what to eat.
Who to screw.
Oh, you'll get snapped up,
no problem.
So, Noah, whereabouts
in the States are you from?
Er, Florida.
Oh, my God, Florida, like Miami?
Come on, Noah.
Party's over.
Dad said
I have to take you home.
I could get a cab.
- Yes, Nick.
- Yo.
- Oi. Love hooking me up, bro.
- Yeah, no worries.
Oh, and I looked after her
for you.
I appreciate that.
- Take that.
- Cheers. Appreciate it.
Yes, sir! Good evening.
So... I realise I may have
jumped the gun
with the whole
"daddy's boy" label.
Giles was telling me
all about your app, Connect.
Sounds cool.
If that was an attempt
of an apology, then I accept.
I'm not apologising.
It's not me
that needs to apologise.
Hmm. So you think it's OK to
judge people indiscriminately?
I was judging you based
on information I'd acquired.
- That's bullshit.
- It's not bullshit.
- That's a lie.
- No, it's not. OK, fine!
If I were to judge you
right now,
I'd say you're being
pretty rude.
- You think that's fair?
- I think that's generous.
Have you seen the way you've
treated me since I arrived?
Parenting 101. Teach your kids
to be polite to guests.
Don't talk about my parents.
Oh, your parents...
Don't.
Have I finally found the
perfect child's Achilles heel?
He's not a daddy's boy,
but maybe he's a mommy's boy.
I'd hate to not live up
to your expectations.
Hey. Why are you... Why are you
getting out of the car?
What the hell?
Get out.
- Get out.
- OK. Fine.
Enjoy your walk, yeah?
You're gonna
leave me on the sidewalk
in the middle of a city
I don't know?
No, I'm gonna leave you
on the pavement.
You're kidding me?
You're being insane right now!
Wow! Wow!
Shit!
Hello?
Nick Leister's sister?
It's Zach. I'm the valet.
He told me to come pick you up.
Oh, he did, did he?
Well, that's nice of him.
And straight home, by the way.
Not to the party
or anywhere else.
Straight home.
You know what, Zach?
I'm not quite ready to go home.
Keep up, keep up.
Sorry.
And you're sure Nick'll be here?
Yeah, a hundred.
There's no party without Nick.
Friends, Romans, contraband.
My boy.
You got me a happy meal, yeah?
And a toy.
OK, I'm gonna go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
Hold on.
Er, it's all right,
we're all friendly.
Um, my name's Tom.
Free to have a look around.
Hope you like to party.
Hey, let's go,
let's go, let's go.
He's over here.
I'll take that as a "yes".
♪ Welcome to the jungle
where we go mental ♪
where we go mental... ♪
- Hey, Nick.
- Oi!
What the fuck is your problem?
I did not know
she was gonna do that.
What is wrong with you?
Leaving me on the sidewalk?
Really?
I could have been robbed!
What if I was killed?
You're gonna wish you were,
you little bitch!
♪ Von Dutch,
cult classic in your eardrums ♪
♪ Why you lying? You won't fuck
unless he's famous ♪
♪ Do that little dance,
without it, you'd be nameless ♪
♪ It's so obvious
I'm your number one ♪
♪ I'm your number one,
yeah, it's so obvious ♪
I'm your number one ♪
♪ I'm your number one,
yeah, it's so obvious... ♪
Noah?
Whoa!
Have you taken something? Huh?
Did somebody give you this?
Hey, hey, look at me.
Did somebody give this to you?
I think I'm the toy. For Tom.
Where's Tom?!
What is it, mate?
You want a kiss?
- Oh!
- Don't say anything.
Yeah, she's cute, huh, Nick?
Cos it's you,
maybe I'll share my ride.
Oh, my days! Nick, bruv!
- What the fuck?
- Fuck, man.
You good, bro?
Oh, my God.
No, I'm not good, man!
Oh, he's just smashed my nose.
- Hey, Nick, Nick.
- Get the door.
Bro, on my life...
- I told her, she's not coming.
- Get in.
She persuaded me to come!
Mind games.
Who made this car so low?
- You had one job, Zach!
- Mind games.
- One job!
- Fuck's sake, man!
How are you feeling?
If you don't remember,
I can enlighten you.
Look, nothing bad happened, OK?
I brought you home.
Nothing bad? Does being drugged
not count as bad to you?
Does punching someone
not count as bad?
I'm sorry. Last time I checked,
you weren't invited,
so you shouldn't
have been there.
You should take a real good look
at your choice of friends, Nick.
Does William know about the
crowd his wonder boy hangs with?
- Maybe I should enlighten him.
- No, don't.
Don't. OK?
I'd appreciate it if you
kept it to yourself. OK?
So let's just stick to the plan
and keep out
of each other's way.
Hey!
How are you?
♪ Oh no, I did it again ♪
♪ I let my mind leak out
into all my friends ♪
♪ And now I'm lonely,
sitting and sink in the blue ♪
♪ Oh no, I did it again ♪
♪ I let myself inside
till the silence ends ♪
♪ I hope you call me ♪
♪ Slipping and thinking
of you ♪
♪ I'm caving out ♪
♪ And I just sit back
while I watch me drown ♪
♪ So I'm safe and sound ♪
♪ While I'm in this room,
no, it's nothing new ♪
♪ Slipping and thinking
of you ♪
of you... ♪
- Suits you.
- Um, er...
Sorry, I was just, er...
Snooping.
Hmm.
I'll be out tonight
if you need more time.
No, no.
Oh, my...
Asshole!
- What are you doing?
- I'm coming with you.
- You won't like where I'm going.
- OK.
♪ Meet me out of town ♪
♪ I want to take the roof down
for a ride ♪
♪ Would you, would you
take me out of town? ♪
♪ Baby, baby,
let's go out tonight ♪
♪ When I saw you there... ♪
Oh, we're here.
Cool.
My car's better
than yours, though.
You know what I mean?
Hey.
Nice wheels.
What, you lost?
Bye, babe.
Custom paint, right?
- Bola FLY spokes?
- Yeah.
One point eight turbo?
- Two hundred brakes?
- Two-fifty.
Cool.
- See you later.
- I'm Jenna.
I'm Noah.
What's your story, then, Noah?
How long you got?
Come on.
Step into my office.
Ah, babe.
- Oh, that's, that's bad.
- Yeah.
You know, that's my car.
A gift to her as I left.
- Oh, babe, I'm so sorry.
- Yeah.
- Oh, that sucks.
- Yeah, it does.
But at least
you're rid of him now, man.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, sorry, man.
What brings you here, then?
Er, my mom married
this British guy,
so... here I am.
How's it going?
Didn't exactly have
a welcoming committee.
His son's a real asshole.
So you got two shit men
in your life, then, yeah?
Guess so.
Here.
I'm giving you my number.
You need at least
one decent friend.
And I like a girl
who knows her cars.
Yeah, well, my dad raced,
so I've been around them
my whole life.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
And what,
is he still on the track?
Not something
you can do a lot of from jail.
Mad.
But what, you got
the racing gene, then, yeah?
- Yeah, I guess so.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
He taught me how to drive
before he taught me to walk.
And then I won a bunch
of kart races, you know,
NASCAR Youth.
You know the drill.
I really don't, babe.
I got my licence last year.
- Yeah, man.
- No way!
- Yeah.
- So what about you?
Have you got a dad in prison
and a cheating ex-boyfriend,
or just me?
That is just you, babe.
- OK.
- Very specific story, though.
Drove so fast that
he wrapped it round a tree,
and nearly took both of us out,
yeah.
Hey, Jenna, you hear they're
setting up to race later?
That's if the cops don't show.
Whose grand idea was that?
Yours?
There's a race?
No, babe, in the UK,
we don't race.
Yeah, we cruise and we drift
and we pose,
but we don't race
cos we get shut down.
And you know that.
Don't make that face, neither.
Yes, mate,
I love your girlfriend so much.
Ah, babe.
This is my boyfriend, Lion.
And this is our good friend,
Nick.
- Hi, babe. This is Noah.
- Noah.
She just moved here from Florida
to live with her stepdad
and a dickhead of a son.
So you two know each other,
then, yeah?
OK.
So how do you know Nick?
From school?
Nah, Lion turned down
his offer from Cambridge.
- Didn't you, mate?
- I did that. I did that.
No, I own a boxing gym
over in Brixton, yeah.
And one day,
this posh kid wanders in
and said he wants to learn
to fight, you know, so...
Nick fights? Like... in a ring?
Yeah. Yeah. Nick fights, yeah.
Not many that can beat him.
Not even me.
Not even Knuckles.
Lion started taking him
to these bare-knuckle fights.
They're fuckin' brutal, babe.
Yeah, look, I like to watch,
you know, have a gamble,
but, er, Nick being Nick
wanted to join in, you know.
Yeah, he was in a pretty
dark place back then, man.
- Speak of the devil.
- Yo.
You all right, mate?
What's up with you?
What do you think
is up with her, bro?
Her best friend
just smashed her boyfriend.
- How would you be?
- What, for real?
Yeah, whatever. It's fine.
Babe, you got two options, yeah?
Either we send a kiss pic back,
or get messy.
- Messy?
- Messy.
- What do you mean, messy?
- Messy, man. Dance?
- Yeah.
- Messy?
♪ Let's ride ♪
♪ Lavender Lamborghini,
roll up in a blue bikini ♪
♪ Bitches on the beaches
looking super cute and freaky ♪
♪ All my friends
are princesses ♪
♪ We keep it whipped
and creamy ♪
♪ Ice cubes on our tongues ♪
♪ Because we like
to keep it freezy ♪
♪ Lavender Lamborghini,
get out on the right side ♪
♪ Chauffeur stayed at home ♪
♪ Because my girl
wanted to ride ♪
♪ Looking luxe and tasting
plush, I'm feeling so alive ♪
♪ Want to take it
to the highway ♪
♪ Come on,
let's go for a drive ♪
♪ All my life, I've been
waiting for a good time ♪
♪ A good time ♪
♪ Let me ride, let me ride ♪
♪ All my life, I've been
waiting for a good time ♪
♪ So let's ride... ♪
Come with me.
♪ Bitches know
they can't catch me ♪
♪ Beep, beep, so let's ride ♪♪
Just trust me.
Did you mean what you said?
What?
About wanting to hurt your ex?
Dan? Sure.
If I could burn his collection
of pretentious movie tees,
I'd feel...
I'll send them to you and you
can use them however you want.
OK.
I ain't having
this conversation anymore.
For reals. Obviously, I ain't.
No, I ain't betting against him.
I ain't betting against my bro.
He's gonna lose.
What are you doing, man?
What was that?
It's him. He's putting down
a month's wages on Nick
winning some race
against Ronnie.
Nick fights and races?
Any other bad-boy clichés?
This is Ronnie, man.
He's just come out
of a year in prison.
He's a proper bad guy.
Gun-for-hire-type bad.
He's always hated Nick, man.
He thinks he's some spoiled
rich-arse kid.
Now he's got it
into his maniac head
that Nick's been
disrespecting him,
because he's the only one
who stands up to him.
But when Ronnie asks you to
race, you can't say no, yeah?
Don't keep me waiting,
boy. Come on.
What's the track?
Er, it's out that way
and through the tunnel.
There's only one way
this is ending.
It's with Nick losing.
Oi, Leister, let's not keep
the people waiting, mate.
Come on, let's go.
Bro, don't let him get in
your head. You got this.
Who's in my car?
Let's go, Nicky!
So... who's driving the car?
Yeah, come on.
OK, it's on.
She wasn't even
supposed to be here bro,
now she's in the car!
This ain't a joke.
What's she playing at?
Bro, she's good.
This means
the bet's void, right?
Ronnie's gonna kill us, bro.
Have a bit of this, mate.
Come on, come on!
Oh, you shit!
No way! She said her dad
taught her to drive.
Apparently, he's some
big-deal racer or something.
Come on, come on.
Who the fuck is that?
That is not Nick.
Who the hell
is living in my house?
What the...
No chance!
Come on!
You have got to be
fucking kidding me.
Get out of the way. Move, man!
Oh, you have no idea
what you've just done.
Nick.
If I challenge you to race,
yeah, I expect you to race.
Relax, Ronnie, yeah?
It was a mistake.
No, it was me, I got in the car.
Nick didn't even know.
I heard you got a bit comfy
while I've been away.
- Broke Tom at his own party.
- He deserved it.
Are you gonna shut that up
or shall I?
Not my nose again!
Hey, yo, police!
- Yo, yo, Nick!
- This ain't over, Nick.
If you won't race,
then we fight.
No gloves. No bell.
Just me and you. Nothing else.
You hear me?
We need to go!
See you later, Nicky boy.
Get Daddy to buy you
a nice coffin, yeah?
Noah! Oi, Noah!
Noah! We need to go. Come on!
Now get in the car!
We have the same tattoo.
I know.
I noticed yours the other night.
So, Jenna tells me your dad
taught you to drive like that.
I don't talk about my dad.
I'm sorry about tonight.
I had no idea me racing would...
Yeah, it was stupid.
I'm really, really angry
with you.
Right now,
I'm just checking you're OK.
- Tomorrow, I will be angry.
- Thanks for the heads-up.
Was that a panic attack?
Yeah.
Do you know what causes 'em?
Sometimes it's small spaces.
Sometimes the dark.
But... mostly violence.
Please don't fight Ronnie.
I don't have a choice.
There's always a choice.
Nick.
I just wanted to say thanks.
For the kiss.
No problem.
I'd do it for anyone.
- Oh, yeah?
- Hmm.
Lion?
Giles?
- Zach?
- I don't trust Zach.
Plus he never has a clean shave,
so...
I don't know.
There's something about
a... five o'clock shadow
that does something to me.
Shame it's only just after four.
Goodnight.
Have you spoken to Dan?
How's he doing?
More importantly,
how are you doing?
Actually, pretty good.
Good.
Oh, Nick, I've just seen
your eye. What...?
Yeah, he did it last night
at boxing.
Crumpet?
Right. I'm gonna go see Maddie,
so I'll probably stay overnight.
Well, I think
you should take Noah with you.
Who's Maddie?
It's a beautiful drive.
You'd love the countryside.
We leave in ten.
Maddie? Who's Maddie?
♪ I'm in my head again
but it's fine ♪
♪ It's fine ♪
♪ Caught myself falling hard,
it's a sign ♪
- ♪ This time ♪
♪ I like to think of you
as mine... ♪
You said ten minutes.
♪ I called you back again,
but it's fine ♪
- ♪ It's fine, it's fine ♪
- ♪ It's fine ♪
♪ We can go
if you'd like to... ♪
Drive slow.
♪ I can't go without you ♪
♪ We can go if you'd like to ♪
♪ I've been running
in circles ♪
♪ You're bruising up my heart,
and I wanna show you ♪
♪ I'll say it like ♪
♪ Please stay cos
I really want you to want me ♪
♪ You say, "OK,
I really want you to want me" ♪
♪ Found you in my head again,
but it's fine ♪
Hey, here we are.
Maddie's house.
Bet she's not expecting me.
Wait.
Who do you think Maddie is?
No, Maddie is my sister,
and that's my mother.
Oh, my God, you've gotten big!
I still can't believe
you let her drive your car.
Yeah, to be fair, I can't
believe it either.
Can I drive it?
I'd let you drive.
I don't know about Mum.
I don't know how Mum
would feel about that,
but I'd let you drive.
It was not...
I was safe, I promise.
She was good.
- No, please.
- Let me help.
- Are you sure? I can carry...
- Yes! Relax. I've got this.
OK.
Yeah? You go hide.
Ten seconds.
Ten, nine...
She's great.
- She's cute, isn't she?
- Yeah.
We're playing hide and seek.
I've got about a minute.
She's absolutely terrible at it.
- Your mum's great, too.
- Yeah.
How old were you
when they split up?
Er... she actually left
when I was 12.
And when did you reconnect?
Er, like, two years ago,
something like that.
How did that...?
All right, what is this,
an interrogation?
Sorry, I was just curious.
I'm joking.
Just joking.
The deal between me and my mum
is that I can continue
to see Maddie
as long as
I stay out of trouble.
Which means no fighting.
As long as I play by her rules,
I get to see the most
important woman in my life.
I don't think your girlfriend
would care to hear that.
Who?
I don't know. The girl
you went to the gala with?
The one you hang with and...
Anna and I are just friends.
Does she know that?
Nick, come find me!
Five? Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Ready or not, here I come.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Maddie! Where are you?
Just disappeared!
Yeah, it looks like confetti.
It does look like confetti.
- You're so right. It's pretty.
- I wasn't going to say,
but you can't expect me
not to notice.
You're being ridiculous.
Why isn't William
keeping tabs on you?
I was in the ring.
You don't get cuts like these
wearing gloves, Nick,
so stop lying to me.
Mum won't let Nick
come to my football match.
No street fights,
no racing and no drugs,
or you lose your privileges
with Maddie.
OK, this wasn't my fault.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Your body is your own.
I'm not gonna deal
with this shit.
I'm gonna go get a drink.
Here.
Thank you.
He won't be far.
He just...
needs to blow off steam.
I think it's great
you two have reconnected.
Oh, well...
Would have been nice if I hadn't
had to leave in the first place.
I, um...
I was... well, am an alcoholic.
Did he tell you that?
I left him and his dad
because I needed to get well.
During my treatment, I tried
to reach out to Nick, but...
he, er...
He wasn't ready.
So for years,
Nick has been trying to deal
with all this by himself.
All the anger he feels for me
comes out through his fists.
Or on the road.
Families can be complicated,
can't they?
Welcome to ours, Noah.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Maybe. I don't know, er...
I'm sorry,
you've got your own shit.
Yeah, but Dan's
thousands of miles away, so...
Which is lucky,
or I'd punch his lights out.
Which wouldn't improve
the situation with your mom.
I don't care.
If you were mine,
I'd never let anyone hurt you.
Nick...
I want you more
than I've ever wanted anyone.
Nick?
Is that you?
I'll be right there.
Shit, Noah.
What the hell
are you doing to me?
See you in the morning.
Please, stop.
But I want him to be there.
Maddie, we spoke about this.
OK, I'll see you very soon, OK?
And I will come
and watch you play, I promise.
Yeah? Give me a hug.
All right, come on, run along.
- I'll see you later Mum, yeah?
- Hey. Hey.
This is your last chance.
No more illegal fights.
All right, I've got it.
- OK. Look, you understand?
- Yes.
Maddie loves you so much.
You don't want to let her down.
Oh...
Such a hypocrite.
Let's go.
Er, do you have plans later?
- Do you wanna, like, watch a...
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm busy. Sorry.
Hey, what's... what's going on?
Look, I just need
to stay out of trouble.
And I'm trouble, right?
You're not afraid
your mom's gonna find out
about your fight with Ronnie?
About the underground racing?
I didn't race, you did.
And now I have to fight Ronnie
because of that.
Hello?
Mom?!
- Surprise!
- Oh, my God!
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, my God.
Oh!
Oh, I missed the surprise.
Are you surprised?
Yeah.
That's all right, Martin.
The keys were in my bag.
I know!
Your mom invited me to visit.
She said that
maybe you missed me?
- Hug?
- Get out.
Noah, please, look, I made
a mistake, OK? Never ever again.
- Trust me.
- Trust you?
Yes. I wouldn't be here
if I didn't want this.
Dan, come on!
Oh, my God, Noah,
I was so cut up when you left.
OK? I lost my girlfriend
and my best friend.
I admit that what I did
was a colossal mistake,
for which I deserve
to be chastised.
But don't punish us, OK?
What we have.
We're so good, Noah.
I didn't wanna have
to give you up without a fight,
but if you want me to leave,
then I will.
Colossal and chastised?
- I might have looked them up.
- Pathetic.
OK.
If you stay, it's as a friend.
A shitty friend.
OK?
It's a nice house.
We should get out.
Go and see Buckingham Palace
and the wheel,
and Windsor Castle.
I don't know, London stuff.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you so much, Emily.
- That was delicious.
- Mm-hmm.
I didn't sleep last night.
Texting Haley?
Fair.
No, I... Look.
I'll do anything, OK,
to make this work.
I just want you back, Noah.
Hey.
N-No, we weren't...
I think your brother can read
the room, Noah.
How you doing? I'm Dan.
Noah's boyfriend.
Cool shirt.
Yeah. "Life moves pretty fast.
If you don't stop and look
around once in a while,
you could miss it."
No? It's, er,
Ferris Bueller's Day Off.
Yeah, I know.
What a dick.
Wait, is that the, er...
the guy from the photos?
It is, isn't it?
OK. Well, er...
That'll never work.
Back together, then?
Kiss me.
Wait.
Not here.
♪ So I got edges
that scratch... ♪
Here.
♪ And sometimes,
I don't got a filter ♪
♪ But I'm so tired of eating ♪
♪ All of my misspoken words ♪
Here.
♪ I know my disposition
gets confusing ♪
♪ My disproportionate reactions
fuse with my eager state ♪
♪ That's why you wanna come out
and play with me... ♪
- Here.
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Why? ♪
Don't hurt him.
But make him leave.
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Stooped down and out ♪
♪ You got me
begging for thread ♪
♪ To sew this hole up
that you ripped in my head... ♪
Hey, buddy, how's it going?
You haven't seen my girlfriend
around, have you?
Think you lost the privilege
of calling her that
when you shagged
her best friend.
I'll give you $1,000
to get on a plane
back to where you came from.
Fifteen hundred?
You really got a thing for her,
don't you?
It's a little bit sick though,
isn't it?
But I think you know that.
I think she knows it, too.
Likes it.
Fifteen hundred?
I'd have paid ten grand,
you cheap shit.
Do you know,
I think you should take him.
Oh, I'd love to.
I have a surprise for you.
Are there body parts in there?
It's not quite that good.
No!
I have a fire and a bag
of pretentious movie tees.
Do with them as you will.
I cannot believe you.
- What?
- Get it in there.
- OK.
- OK, right.
- Ready?
- Three... Oh.
Oh, sorry!
- Yes.
- Let's go again.
- Look at it go.
- Get rid of that immediately.
- No, that's going straight in.
- Imagine him wearing that!
That is going
straight in. On three.
OK, this is great.
I feel better.
- You feel better?
- Yeah, I feel it.
- Weight lifted?
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- OK.
- OK, next.
Get it in.
- You put this one in.
- OK, right.
- Get ready.
- Goodbye, Daniel.
- Forever. Boom.
- Forever.
- Oh!
- Ooh!
Bye-bye.
OK, stay right there.
I'm gonna go get something.
♪  Oh, yeah ♪
♪ I'm Miss American Dream
since I was 17 ♪
♪ Don't matter
if I step on the scene ♪
♪ Or sneak away
to the Philippines ♪
♪ They still gon' put pictures ♪
♪ Of my derriere
in the magazine... ♪
♪ You want a piece of me?
You want a piece of me? ♪
♪ I'm Mrs "Lifestyles
of the Rich and Famous" ♪
♪ You want a piece of me? ♪
♪ I'm Mrs "Oh, my God,
that Britney's Shameless" ♪
♪ You want a piece of me? ♪
♪ I'm Mrs "Extra! Extra!
This just in" ♪
♪ You want a piece of me? ♪
♪ I'm Mrs "She's Too Big,
Now She's Too Thin" ♪
♪ You want a piece of me? ♪♪
I need some good vibes, man!
What are you smiling about?
I'm making 20K
if he wins tonight, babe.
Twenty grand! Twenty racks!
- You good?
- Yeah. Just thought...
Never mind.
Come on, Nick.
Ready? Ready?
Touch fists. Go.
Come on, Nick.
Fuck's sake, bro. Get up, bro!
Nick! Up! Up!
Jenna,
I think I'm gonna have to go.
But he's winning, man.
This is him winning.
He's never gonna
see Maddie again.
Babe, I gotta go.
I'll be back, OK?
- You just need to focus.
- What did she say?
- Maddie. Something...
Something about Maddie,
all right?
- I'm done.
- What? What, what, what?
- No, no.
- I'm done.
You gotta finish this,
Nick, all right?
- I'm done, bro.
- No. No, no, no, no!
Forget the money, all right?
It's ten seconds, yeah?
Otherwise Ronnie
is coming after you, me.
Please, there's...
there's no other choice.
- There's always a choice.
- Oi, Leister!
Nick. Nick!
Where the hell's he going?
You calling Mummy?
Where's he going?
Where's he going?!
Oi! Fuck's sake!
Leister?
Oi!
Look at me!
Yo, yo, yo, yo!
Don't be a killjoy, Nicky boy.
Party's just getting started.
- What is your problem?
- We're done!
Cos I know you ain't scared!
Well, you should be, boy.
Cos if I ain't coming for you,
then I'm coming for your family.
And then I'm coming
for your friends.
Are we clear?
- We're clear.
- What?
We're clear.
Oi, Ronnie.
And I'm taking your car
as compensation
for what I would have taken
for battering ya.
Cheers for the ride, bro.
Shit!
Come on, man,
I'll drop you home.
Nick.
One birthday breakfast.
With burnt bacon.
It's your favourite.
I was thinking, um...
How about you getting away
to Ibiza with your friends?
For the weekend?
Yeah, that would be really good.
Thank you.
Can Noah come?
Nick!
Come on, you're such an idiot!
Hey, it's my birthday.
You have to be nice.
Well, I heard
what happened at the fight.
You did the right thing.
Thank you.
I did it for you.
Oh, did you? No!
How dare you?
So...
can you guess what I want
for my birthday?
Better taste in music?
Ooh, you love my music.
- Mmm... Not sure.
- I think you do!
Um...
- Some fresh hair dye?
- Ooh!
I know what you want.
A breath mint.
I've just brushed my teeth.
See, to everyone else...
just looks like
we're having a conversation.
So as long as you can keep
your emotions under control...
You think I can't?
Oh, dear.
You nearly fell
at the first hurdle.
Shut up.
Do you want me to stop?
I can stop.
No.
Noah? I'm off!
You two have fun today.
Enjoy your surprise, Nick.
Uh-huh.
Go easy on him, Noah.
Better get ready.
No, you didn't.
- I did. Yes, I did.
- You didn't.
Happy birthday.
To celebrate, I thought
I could teach you how to drive.
You won one race.
♪ I'm overjoyed,
I'm overjoyed ♪
♪ Just standing there
in corduroy ♪
♪ If I told you once, I told
you, boy, I'm overjoyed ♪
♪ I'm overjoyed,
I'm overjoyed ♪
♪ Just standing there
in corduroy ♪
♪ If I told you once, I told
you, boy, I'm overjoyed ♪
♪ You love, definitely, baby ♪
♪ You're God's gift
to every lady ♪
♪ On the dartboard, 180... ♪
- Ladies first.
- I'm a gentleman.
Can't keep up?
Oh, you want to play?
Bring it on.
Oh, just you wait.
Whoo!
Shit!
OK, now I'm coming.
Don't threaten me
with a good time.
Noah,
that jumpsuit you're wearing,
does it zip all the way down?
You're so good
at trying to distract me
but it's not gonna work!
I think the only way
you're gonna catch me
is with a short cut.
Shut up! What do you mean,
short cut?
Bye!
OK, consolation prize.
You didn't?
Got me a new car.
- "Nick, happy birthday.
- Mm-hmm.
Sorry about your car.
Someday,
you'll buy yourself a new one.
From Noah."
You know,
that was my favourite car.
Will you not go to the police?
Nah. There's, like, a code.
You don't talk about Fight Club?
Exactly.
You know the cashier in there
has never had a Twirl?
That is a tragedy.
I can't believe it.
Well, tragedy has struck twice
cos I've never had one either.
No?
I was joking!
Of course I've had a Twirl!
What am I, an alien?
- Whoa!
- Get the fucking door!
Oh, my God!
Get the fucking door!
Oh, my God! Drive! Drive!
Drive!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Fuck's sake!
Now get some sleep.
I don't understand.
Ronnie already took your car.
Something else is going on.
Sorry.
It's all right.
Your touch feels good.
You know it means strength.
I get there's a code, whatever,
but at what point
do we tell someone?
We don't.
I'll deal with Ronnie.
You mean fight him?
I don't fight anymore.
Promise.
Right, let's get some sleep.
Early flight tomorrow.
And I'm not missing it.
Thank you.
So, Nick and Noah, yeah,
are like...?
- Yeah. Take this.
- I'm baffed.
- Thank you. Ah, beautiful.
- Gracias. Gracias, señor.
Noah knows. I know.
Nick doesn't know anyone knows.
- OK.
- So, it's still...
You know what I want, bruv.
Move over.
Do that again, I dare you.
Pardon. Margarita?
- Ah, yes!
- Yes.
- Here you go, here you go.
- Lovely. Thank you.
Hey, you look, like, cosy.
- Cosy.
- So cosy.
I might just go jump
in the middle of you.
Cheers, everyone.
Ibiza, baby.
Let's get messy.
We should get jet skis.
You're such
an adrenaline junkie.
I wish we could just sit down
for ten minutes. Chill.
Well then,
I'm just gonna go swim.
Er, OK, yeah.
You want me to come with you?
You don't have to,
but I'd like it.
- Come on!
- Have a little paddle.
- Yes, yes, yes, yes.
- Have fun. Love you.
- Yeah, love you.
- Kiss.
Talk to me, bro.
What?
What's the sitch
with you and Noah?
Come. Spill the beans.
There is no me and Noah.
Now the problem
with that statement
is I don't know if you're lying
to me or to yourself.
Come.
All right. But let's just say,
for argument's sake,
there was a "me and Noah".
Can you imagine
how messy that would be?
Look, me, personally, bro,
I like messy.
Look, life, yeah?
You get one of 'em.
You gotta do what makes you
happy, all right?
And you know I got you, man,
no matter what.
- Feel me?
- I feel you.
But, now...
Let's party, baby. Let's party.
I wanna get two piña coladas.
- All right, come.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
♪ This could be a good night
for good times ♪
♪ And you look like
a good time ♪
♪ We're dancing
to Dancing in the Moonlight ♪
♪ Now I want you bad ♪
♪ Can you make me feel better? ♪
♪ This could be a good night
for good times ♪
♪ And you look like
a good time ♪
♪ We're dancing
to Dancing in the Moonlight ♪
♪ Now I want you bad ♪
♪ Can you make me
feel better? ♪
♪ Do you think
you're better off alone? ♪
♪ I think you better
come along ♪
♪ Can you make me
feel better? ♪
♪ Do you think
you're better off alone? ♪
♪ I think you better
come along ♪♪
Yo. You good?
Yeah.
What are we gonna do
about Ronnie, bro?
I've heard he's looking for us.
Well, what's the plan?
I don't know.
- "I don't know"?
- No. I'm not fighting anymore.
Bro, this ain't a joke!
That shit you pulled
at the fight, it cost us.
It cost me.
I need you to fight him.
And you gotta let him win.
Or else we'll always
be watching our backs.
Guess I don't
have a choice, then.
Yeah.
Hey. No, no, no.
We're just friends.
Nick!
Get off me.
Nick.
Oi, Nick.
What the hell was that, man?
He was a creep, Jenna.
He had his hands all over her.
Bro, she was fine.
So you thought hitting him
was the right thing to do?
Yeah, well,
it made me feel better.
Well, that just about
sums it up, doesn't it?
It's all about you.
I'm gonna go see if he's OK.
Don't you...
- Nick, Nick. Nick, Nick.
- Babe. Babe, come inside, yeah?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
You know,
I can't do this, because of you.
Because you represent everything
I've been running from.
Noah...
you know I'd never hurt you.
You already have.
Come on, babe.
Noah!
All right, man.
Let's go home.
You know, I've known
Nick a really long time.
And, yeah, he can be a little
bit hot-headed sometimes,
but he's a good guy deep down.
And he's a really good friend.
Maybe don't write him off
straight away.
He's just got weird ways
of showing he cares.
Come on, man, we're at a party.
Drink up.
Posh party too, babe.
Took forever.
- Who invited them?
- Giles did.
Nick's been MIA
ever since she arrived.
She's so pretty, though.
Are you for real right now?
She's so bloody irritating.
I wish she'd just disappear.
It's your party.
Maybe we ought to teach her
a little lesson.
Noah, you don't need
to wait there.
There's another bathroom
on the top floor.
- Oh.
- Come on.
Thanks.
Now!
Seriously?!
God!
Yes!
Come on, guys! Really?
Shit.
I'm going to go find Nick.
That was so much fun.
Shit!
OK.
- Good?
- Good, yeah?
Really good.
You look good.
- You look beautiful, in fact.
- You look cute.
- Cute?
- Have you, er, seen Noah?
Er, I think she went
to the bathroom.
- You and your little boat shoes.
- Cute.
Hey, you.
- Hey.
- You coming for a drink with me?
Er, yeah. Er...
- Come on, this way.
- Yeah, all right, OK.
Help! Help!
I hope you'll be coming
to Bovey Castle next weekend.
You know the whole gang's going,
and it's been months since
we've been shooting together.
- It's always such a laugh.
- Yeah, sure. Maybe.
Nick, what is going on with you?
I've barely heard from you
in weeks.
I'm surprised you even showed up
this evening.
I've just been busy.
OK.
Right, I'm gonna go find Noah.
Why don't you give your sister
some space, Nick?
You've been acting weird
ever since she arrived.
And I've heard a couple
of nasty little rumours.
God forbid they filter back
to your dad.
I've just realised something.
I can't stand you.
OK, fine.
Why isn't he with Anna?
Oh, my God,
he's looking for Noah.
So embarrassing.
Don't say anything.
Help!
What have you done?
Noah? Noah?
Noah?
Noah!
You're just like your mother.
- No, no!
- Noah, it's just me.
Noah! Give me the damn key!
No!
Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
It's just me.
It's just me. It's just me.
Hey, it's me.
I've got you. I've got you.
Look at me.
When he was sober,
he was a decent dad.
Racing was our thing.
Then his drinking got worse
and he got hooked on oxy.
You know, I was thinking,
after I met your mom, that...
if my dad had just sought help,
you know,
like your mom did, then...
maybe things would be different.
He'd never hurt me before.
Six months after that, I was
in court testifying against him.
I put my dad in jail.
Look at me.
It's not your fault.
OK?
None of that is your fault.
He's just a bad guy.
And he's one half of me.
You're not the same.
It's OK.
I'm tough.
Oh, I know!
You know what I want right now?
I want you.
♪ It's in my hair, in my sleep ♪
♪ In my hands, in my teeth ♪
♪ It's in my chair,
it looks like me ♪
♪ And when it stands,
I take my seat ♪
♪ It's in the air
that I breathe ♪
♪ Understand it's up my sleeve ♪
♪ Well, in my head,
it's in my sleep ♪
♪ With my hands,
in my teeth... ♪
♪ In my prayer, I don't speak ♪
♪ But with my hands
and on my knees ♪
♪ When I ask, I receive ♪
♪ Don't play fair,
don't be sweet ♪
♪ It's in the air
that I breathe ♪
♪ Understand
it's up my sleeve ♪♪
Hey.
Noah?
Hello.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
I have to go,
but I'll be right back, OK?
It's Maddie's football match.
Mum said I can take her.
- I'll be here.
- OK.
Go back to bed.
OK.
- Be quiet.
- Yeah.
- You be quiet.
- Yeah, I will.
So, does calling so soon
make me look desperate?
Yep.
No, that's... that's...
that's cool.
And how are you?
You did the drive
with hardly any sleep.
Er, actually, it's...
it's been good. It's, um...
It gave me an opportunity
to talk to Mum
about what you said.
About why she, er...
you know, why she left and...
that maybe it was
the right thing for her to do.
So, I don't know. Like...
Maybe it was.
I just haven't been able
to see it that way.
I'm so proud of you, Nick.
Yeah?
Thought you'd say,
"Told you so."
No, no, that's cool.
- We'll talk later.
- All right, bye. Bye, bye.
♪ It's so crazy lately ♪
♪ You just understand
my feelings ♪
♪ Lately ♪
♪ See I'm capable and fine ♪
♪ And feeling beautified... ♪
I'm really happy we came here.
You were right.
♪ Maybe it's the loving
in your eyes ♪
- ♪ I'm here, see through ♪
- Ah, here he is.
♪ Maybe it's the magic
in the wine ♪
♪ I'm feeling loose ♪
♪ Maybe it's the fact
that every time I fall ♪
♪ I lose it all ♪
♪ But you got me
from my head to my feet ♪
♪ And I'm ready to dive ♪
♪ Right into you ♪
♪ I'm ready to dive ♪
♪ Maybe it's the fact
that every time I fall ♪
♪ I lose it all ♪
♪ But you got me
from my head to my feet ♪
♪ And I'm ready to dive ♪♪
Lion? Lion, you with me, mate?
It's gonna be all right, OK?
Lion! Well, where is he?
Is he in there?
- Yeah, he's in there.
- What happened?
- What's happened?
- It's OK.
He warned you
and you didn't listen.
- I need to see him.
- I'm sorry.
- Are you his girlfriend?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Go and take a seat.
- Are you OK?
- Dad, I need to tell you...
- Nick, not now.
- No, but I need to.
- Not now.
Security are taking Ella and
Noah to a hotel for a few days.
It's not safe here.
- Dad, can we talk now?
- Yeah, we need to.
This is Detective Sato.
This is much bigger
than you or Noah realise.
This way.
I know you're concerned
about him, and I am too,
but I just...
The paramedic said
he would be fine,
and we should just be here
and use this time to relax.
Shall we swim first, steam,
and then sauna?
Is there a right way
you're supposed to do that?
Noah.
Everything's gonna be OK.
William's talking to the police,
we've got security.
Yeah, I know. I just... I wanna
wait for an update, OK?
Meet me downstairs.
This is Ronnie Burns.
He took my McLaren
when I refused to fight.
He smashed up my car.
He beat up Lion.
He said he'd hurt my friends
if I didn't fight him again.
What aren't you getting?
Nick, we believe
Lion's attack...
was down to Noah's father.
Travis McKay.
Sorry, what?
He's out of jail and in the UK.
What? No. It's Ronnie.
Ronnie Burns. You know him.
Yeah, we know Ronnie.
And he's working
for Noah's father, Travis McKay.
That's Noah's dad?
I've seen him before.
He was at the fight and the...
and the petrol station.
He's very dangerous, Nick.
Four years ago,
he attacked Noah.
That's how she got the scar.
He was released a few weeks ago
and violated his parole.
Travelled in
on a stolen passport.
- And then hired Ronnie?
- Mm-hmm. Right.
- What do they want?
- Probably money.
Well, what's their play?
Nick...
Noah.
When they attacked us
in the car, they...
they went for Noah's door.
I thought they were
trying to go for me,
but they must've been
going for Noah.
Oh, my God,
they left Lion here to scare us.
They were smoking us out
and we've just...
we've just played straight
into their hands.
I need to call her.
Hello, Noah.
Can I squeeze in with you?
Is that all right?
Oh, thank you.
So, where shall we go?
Going down.
I really hope
you like surprises.
Cos I love surprises.
Hi, kid.
Go to Daddy. Go, go, go, go.
Code 134.
A missing 18-year-old female.
All units be on alert...
We're checking the hotel.
You're checking the hotel? No,
you're not, you're sat there.
There's one, two, three, four,
five of you and she's out there,
- and you lot are just sat there.
- Oi. Oi, oi, oi.
You need to get that.
This is William Leister.
Am I speaking with Travis?
Yeah,
you're speaking with Travis.
We want to speak to Noah.
I thought you might.
Nick!
- Nick, help!
- Noah, hey, hey.
- Tell us where you are.
- Help, Nick! Help!
- Nick!
- I'll find you.
Please.
- What do you want?
- A million.
Wire it to this account.
- Come on, I know you got it.
- I'll get it.
- Please.
- You have one hour.
Don't hurt her.
You send the cash,
the kid'll be fine.
- I want what's best for Noah.
- Dad, please.
Help!
He's gone.
What did I say
about smoking that shit?
It's not good for you.
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
- Dad, I've got something.
- Nick, where are you?
Ronnie has my McLaren.
My McLaren has a tracker in it.
If I can find the McLaren,
I can find Ronnie.
If I find Ronnie,
I can find Noah.
Nick, I'll tell the police, but
you have to let them handle it.
Oh, shit!
I'll send you the address.
Get the police to follow me.
Hello, Noah.
How's it going, love?
You all right?
You being looked after?
So...
as you've heard,
the plan, right,
is to swap you out for the cash.
Piece of piss.
But I just wanted to let you in
on a little secret.
I'm not really interested
in the money.
I want to eat the rich! But...
Here's my logic, OK?
I'm gonna share this with you
because I think we're gonna
see eye to eye with this.
I get locked up
trying to graft a living,
while the Nicks of the world
breeze through.
Now, is that fair?
Nick thinks he's a hero,
and what do heroes always do?
That's it.
Save the girl. You're my bait.
Oh, Nicky's gonna be so sad!
So sad he didn't get
to say goodbye to ya.
Well, it's tragic, really.
Did you really think
I was gonna let Nick walk away
from another fight?
Where've you been?
I was just making sure
the package is secure.
You don't talk to her.
Didn't say a word to her, mate.
Shit. We have a visitor.
What... what visitor?
- Get Noah.
- How many are there?
It's just Nick.
The cops won't be far behind.
We gotta go.
As long as we have Noah,
they'll bring us the money.
- No, wait, wait, wait!
- Let's go.
Look,
if it's all the same to you,
I'll deal with Nick.
Take this.
Best of British, mate.
On me.
Hello, Nicky. Long time no see.
Where's Noah?
Time to go, kid.
Tell me where she is, Ronnie!
This is all I wanted, Nick.
Little bit of "us" time.
Who's the better man now?
This is all your doing, Nick!
And now she's in there
with a very mean daddy,
and it is all because of you!
- Noah!
- Nick!
- Get in.
Stay back!
I'm not fucking around, kid.
Drive.
Come on! Come on!
OK, Noah, I'm coming.
Fucking Romeo.
Get him off our tail.
Slow down, Noah, slow down.
This kid doesn't give up.
Oh, shit!
Dad, no!
You lose him or I kill him.
- Go!
- Move out!
You feel that? Huh?
I know you do, kid.
I'm nothing like you!
Get lost, Nick.
I knew I'd cash in on you
one day.
- What?
- Yeah.
I just want my money.
Look out!
- Go, go, go, go!
- I am.
Easy!
Hard right! Right, right,
right, right, right. Right!
OK, Noah.
How's this for a short cut?
I think we lost him.
Keep going!
Come on.
Whoa!
Come on!
OK. OK.
Nick!
Get out of the car!
- Nick!
- You move and I shoot!
Nick!
Get back!
Let me go, or I'll shoot her!
This is the end of the road,
kid.
Suspect is down.
Eyes on. Move in.
Hey, look at me,
look at me, look at me.
Oh, my God.
Nick.
Hey, no, it's OK. You're OK.
You're OK, you're OK.
Oh, my God.
It's OK. Hey, look at me.
You're gonna be OK.
Help! Somebody help!
Hey, it's OK, it's OK. Hey!
I never believed in
happy endings.
London was supposed
to be a fresh start.
But it was the end.
The end of my pain,
of blaming myself for things
that weren't my fault.
I was broken before I met Nick.
It turns out the broken ones
have the power
to heal each other.
We were eternally tied together.
A knot that could
never be broken.
It might not be a happy ending.
But that's because
our story isn't over.
What's happening? Good?
Noah, your mother's a bluffer.
- I can see in her eyes.
- You don't stand a chance.
She's a bluffer.
Ah! Ha-ha!
- Thank you.
- For you.
- Ah, thank you, babe.
- Thanks, Noah.
- Appreciate you.
- Can you open mine, too?
Yeah.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
Hey.
♪ Honey, I'm spiralling... ♪
This is why we have
to appreciate the sun
while it lasts! Come on!
I think we can survive
a little rain, don't you?
Are we doing this?
♪ Just tread lightly... ♪
I knew it wouldn't last.
- Go and get dry.
- Where's Nick and Noah?
Um... I don't know.
Look at you!
I know they're getting along,
but...
- Yeah?
- You don't think they're...
No! No, I don't!
- Well...
- No.
Cos if they were...
- Big problem.
- ♪ Come on, try me ♪
♪ Come on, try me ♪
♪ Cos it's not like
in the movies ♪
♪ You come over, try to fix me ♪
♪ So, if you
can face the facts ♪
♪ Go ahead ♪
♪ And, baby, dive in ♪
♪ Baby, dive ♪
♪ Oh, baby, dive in ♪
♪ I ruin everything ♪
♪ Everything ♪
♪ So I'll give you
a fair warning ♪
♪ So you got time to run ♪
♪ And if you're not down ♪
♪ That's cool,
don't waste my time ♪
♪ Cos I'd rather watch
Real Housewives ♪
You're such a liar, Camille!
♪ Cos it's not like
in the movies ♪
♪ You come over, try to fix me ♪
♪ So, if you
can face the facts ♪
♪ Go ahead ♪
♪ And, baby, dive in ♪
♪ Baby, dive ♪
♪ Oh, baby, dive in ♪
♪ And, baby, dive in ♪
♪ Baby, dive ♪
♪ Baby, dive ♪♪
♪ How did we get here? ♪
♪ We seem all right ♪
♪ I'm just trying to make sense
of the madness ♪
♪ How do I tell you? ♪
♪ Cos I'm so tongue-tied ♪
♪ Making sure
I make it worth it ♪
♪ Just this time ♪
♪ Oh, if you hold me,
then who holds you? ♪
♪ Oh, if you hold me ♪
♪ Are we still a secret
if I told you? ♪
♪  When it's late night
and you're looking at me ♪
♪ In the half-light ♪
♪ We can make it simple ♪
♪ It's complicated
but I don't hate it ♪
♪ Wanna move forward
instead of looking back ♪
♪ I'm just figuring out
where my head's at ♪
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
♪ It's kinda confusing
when I can't think straight ♪
♪ I'm just trying to make sure
that it's worth the wait ♪
♪ Oh, if you hold me,
then who holds you? ♪
♪ Are we still a secret
if I told you? ♪
♪ When it's late night
and you're looking at me ♪
♪ In the half-light ♪
♪ We can make it simple ♪
♪ It's complicated
but I don't hate it ♪
♪ When it's late night
and you're looking at me ♪
♪ In the half-light ♪
♪ I know what you're thinking
without saying much ♪
♪ We feel the rush ♪
♪ We feel the rush,
we feel the rush ♪
we feel good ♪
♪ We feel the rush,
we feel the rush ♪
we feel good ♪
♪ We feel the rush,
we feel the rush ♪
we feel good ♪
♪ We feel the rush ♪
♪ When it's late night
and you're looking at me ♪
♪ In the half-light ♪
♪ We can make it simple ♪
♪ It's complicated
but I don't hate it ♪
♪ No, I don't hate it ♪
♪ When it's late night
and you're looking at me ♪
♪ In the half-light ♪
♪ I know what you're thinking ♪
♪ We don't say much ♪
♪ We feel the rush ♪♪